targethero.com 2012-06-08

# Privacy policy | TargetHero

**TargetHero email marketing solutions is committed to personal privacy and the ethical use of email business and marketing communications.**

This statement discloses the privacy practices of TargetHero™. 

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

  * All TargetHero users have agreed to the “terms and conditions” including a guarantee that all users in their lists have explicitly requested to receive email from their company (opt-in procedure). TargetHero will take all necessary steps including legal actions against any customer that is found in breach of the terms and conditions.
  * All TargetHero users account information is held in strict confidence. We do not sell or share our customer lists with any other entities.
  * At all times, our customers retain ownership and control of their lists and list information. **TargetHero does not rent, trade or sell email addresses.**
  * Personal information such as name, title, email address, website address, phone number, etc. are stored in our databases for the sole purpose of providing the services described on this web site.
  * You may unsubscribe at any time from any of the mailing lists held in our system. Any emails sent from our system will always contain an unsubscribe auto-remove link. Unsubscribing from any list will ensure you will never receive anymore email from that specific list.

### Email and Direct Response Contact

All of our direct response methods are opt-in. If you subscribed to the list of one of our users but do not want to receive it in the future, please follow the “unsubscribe” instructions contained in the body of the email. 

### Security

TargetHero takes precautions to protect data regarding our customers and their lists of users and prospects. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information. The servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment behind firewalls and protection encryption algorithms. 

### Trademarks

The name “TargetHero” is a registered trademark owned by ActiveTrail Ltd. The trademarks, tradenames, service marks and logos (“Trademarks”) used and displayed on this Website are registered and unregistered Trademarks of TargetHero. No display or use of such Trademarks may be made without the express prior written permission of TargetHero. 

### General

We may change our privacy policy in the future. Any changes to our privacy policy will be made available online. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, the practices of this website, or your dealings with our company, please [click here](mailto:info@targethero.com) or send an email to [info@targethero.com](mailto:info@targethero.com). Please see our Spam Policy.
